《神探飞机头》
小心！做得好…
Heads up! Good defense!Good defense!
（玻璃 小心轻放）
我们进城去
We're going downtown.
闭嘴 笨狗
Shut the hell up, you stupid mutt!
什么事？
What do you want?
HDS公司送包裹 是给你的
HDS, sir. How are you this afternoon? Alrighty. I have a package for you.
似乎碎了
It sounds broken.
是的 但相信一定是好货色！
Most likely. I'll bet it was something nice.
这是保险赔偿表格
This is an insurance form.
请在这儿签名
If you'll just sign here, here, and here…
剩下的表格会尽速送上
we'll get the rest of the forms to you soon.
好可爱的狗 我可以摸摸它吗？
That's a lovely dog.Do you mind if I pet him?
我才不在乎
I don't give a rat's ass.
老弟…
Oh, brother…
可以了 剩下的由我填吧
That's fine. I can finish the rest.
再见 保重
You just have yourself a good day. Take care now. Bye-bye.
对不起 HDS
Excuse me! HDS!
请让一让 我可拿着个包裹！
HDS! Coming through!Got a package, people!
你守着门干嘛
Get away from the door.
你怎么回事？滚开？
What's the matter with you? I said, get!
（你中计了）
（宠物侦探王牌威龙留）
真该死
Son of a bitch!
真是险过剃头啊！
That was a close one!
不幸的是
Unfortunately…
比赛中总有失败者
in every contest there must be a loser.
失…败…者
Loohooserrhher.
饿吗？伙伴
Hungry, fellow?
自便吧
There you go.
没事的 火花塞湿了而已
No problem. It gets flooded.
只需稍等一下就好
We'll just wait a few seconds.
或者现在就试试吧
Or we can try it now.
杂种
Putz!
滚下车！
Get out! Get out!
浑蛋总是无处不在的
Assholes are closer than they appear!
帮我推一把！老兄
Give me a push while you're back there.
他好像不肯
Alrighty, then.
发动了！
It's alive!
（失踪西施狗）
（发现即电王牌威龙）
宝贝 过来 挂念妈妈吗？
My little baby, come here. You missed Mommy, didn't you?
当然了 你爸爸有否伤害你？
Yes, you did. Did Daddy hurt you?
我不会让他那样做的？
I won't let him. No, I won't.
他可保留那电视
He can keep the big TV.
但不能伤害你
but he's not gonna hurt my baby, no he's not.
谢谢你
Thank you, Mr. Ventura.
我该如何报答你？
How can I ever repay you?
付酬劳即可
A reward would be good.
我的车有点损坏 又要加汽油
There is some damage to my car, and I had to fill it with premium.
可否替你脱裤子代替付款？
Would you like for me to take your pants off instead?
让我考虑一下
Gee! Let me think.
好的
Sure.
这区的人可真友善
People are real friendly around here.
（没空调的海边房子 出租中）
威龙？
Ventura!
什么事 撒旦？
Yes, Satan?
对不起 单从声音认不出你
I'm sorry, sir. You sounded like someone else.
没关系 王牌威龙…
Never mind the wisecracks, Ventura.
你欠租很久了！
You owe me rent.
我已说过欠你的钱会优先处理
Mr. Shickadance, I told you, you're my first priority.
我正插手一宗大案
I'm on a very big case right now. Check this out.
你看…
Look at that.
那是一只白蚀鸽
That's a true albino pigeon.
富翁的 悬赏二万五千的
Some rich guy lost it. He's offering a $25, 000 reward.
我找到这鸟就还你钱
As soon as I find this bird…
我听到这儿有动物叫声
I heard animals in there.
今早又听到它们四处抓东西
I heard them again this morning, scratching around.
我从不把工作带回家的
I never bring my work home with me.
那些狗粮又是什么回事？
What's all this pet food for?
我要吃多点纤维高的食物
Fiber.
要不要进来看看？来吧！
Wanna take a look inside? Come on!
进来吧！
Come on!
看吧
Go ahead. Snoop around!
满意了吧？
Are you satisfied?
千万别让我捉到你带动物回来
Just don't let me catch you with an animal in here. That's all.
好吧 保重 再见
All right.Take care, now. Bye-bye, then.
失败者
Loser!
来吧 森林之友
Come to me, jungle friends.
罗杰 我问你们一个问题
Roger, let me ask you one question.
一条五万磅重的鱼怎会不见的
How in hell do you lose a 500-pound fish?
什么？
What?
对不起 我想说那不是鱼…
I'm sorry, I was just going to say…
…是哺乳类动物
that it's not a fish. It's a mammal.
谢谢你 科学家小姐
Thank you, Miss Jacques Cousteau.
她无恶意的
She didn't mean anything by that.
我才不担心那鱼
I don't give a good goddamn about that fish!
如果你喜欢 可拿它做鱼柳
Fillet it and fast-food it if you want to!
我只想赢超级杯
All I give a damn about is winning the Super Bowl!
要想胜利 至少要令球员安心
My athletes have got to have their heads in the right place!
你已入这行那么久了
Shit, Roger! You've been in this business a long time.
你知道那些球员是多迷信！
You know how superstitious these players are.
高中后那四分卫便把袜子倒穿
I have a quarterback that's put his socks on backwards since high school.
后卫两年没洗过护阴
I've got a linebacker that hasn't washed his jockey strap in two years…
因为他认为苍蝇能带来好运
because he thinks flies are lucky.
现在我要那条鱼在大赛日登场
I want that fish on that field Super Bowl Sunday.
寻回那条鱼或是另找新差事吧
Find the fish…or find new jobs!
为何要选这时候？大赛两周前
Why did it happen now, two weeks before the Super Bowl?
一定是动物权益组织的人干的
I'll tell you, it's those animal-rights activists!
老是高举他们的标语
Always out with their signs:
「动物生而自由 别虐待雪花」
"Animals were born free! Stop torturing Snowflake!"
那条鱼的生活比我们都好
That fish lives better than they do.
罗杰 警方现在已经着手调查了
The police are checking into the animal-rights groups.
警方对这件事 有回音吗？
Have they called back?
没有 但我想告诉你 我的「可图」走失时
No, but I wanted to tell you, when I lost my Cuddles…
我请了宠物侦探
I hired a pet detective.
请什么？
A what?
宠物侦探
A pet detective.
谢了 但还是交给专业人士做吧
Thanks, Martha, but we better leave this to professionals.
他相当不错的
Well, actually, he was quite good.
侦查宠物是一门深奥的学问
Pet detection is a very involved, highly scientific process.
如穿手套
Like a glove!
威龙来了
Mr. Ventura here to see you.
- 谢谢你 - 我是玛莉莎
- Thanks, Martha. - Hi, I'm Melissa Robinson.
幸会
Pleasure to meet you.
进来时有麻烦吗？
Any trouble getting in?
没有 戴胶手套的人很温柔
No, the guy with the rubber glove was surprisingly gentle.
大赛一周前 保安很严格
Security's tight Super Bowl week.
请坐 我开门见山说了
Why don't you have a seat? I'll get right to the point.
昨晚我们的吉祥物被盗
Our mascot was stolen from his tank last night.
你知道是什么来的吗？
Are you familiar with Snowflake?
不知道
Negative.
从迈哈密海洋馆得来的
We got him from Miami.
是罕有的长鼻海豚
He's a rare bottle-nosed dolphin.
这是它在半场休息时的新表演
This is a new trick he was going to do for the halftime show.
来吧！海豚 我们开始吧！
Let's go.
太好了
All right!
海豚 再来
Come on, let's go!
好傢伙
Good boy!
要烟灰缸吗？
Would you like an ashtray?
我不吸烟 很讨人厌的
I don't smoke.It's a disgusting habit.
警方今天来过
The police came today.
很明显绑匪从后门进来 像是用…
Apparently, the kidnappers came in through the back with a…
四轮传动 开背式的客货车
Four-wheel-drive van, loaded from the rear.
海豚失踪有否带来麻烦 罗杰
Roger, how you holding up?
如果我被炒鱿鱼时面呈怪相…
If I'm walking funny it's.
是因为要应付太多记者
because I got two dozen reporters up my ass.
他们整天问我雪花的事
They've been asking me about Snowflake all morning.
他是什么人？
Who's he?
这是普罗杰 这是威龙
Roger Podacter, meet Ace Ventura.
他是我聘请的宠物侦探
He's our pet detective.
幸会 梅玛莎小姐极推荐你的
Nice to meet you. You came very highly recommended by Martha Mertz.
梅玛莎？
Martha Mertz?
噢 对 那条母狗
Oh, yeah, the bitch!
什么？
Waht?
北京狗 在高原公园失踪
Pekingese, lost in Highland Park area.
我找到它时半死不活的
She was half-dead when I found her.
那是水池吗？失陪了
Is that the tank?Excuse me.
- 警方放干的？- 是 今早
- Cops drain it? - Yes, this morning.
如果我五分钟内不回来…
If I'm not back in five minutes…
那再多等一会
just wait longer.
队长日志 星际日期23.9
Captain's log, stardate 23.9, rounded off to the nearest decimal point.
我们重回过去 拯救一古生物
We've traveled back in time to save an ancient species from annihilation.
目前尚没海洋生物痕迹
So far…no signs of aquatic life,
但无论如何 我定要找到它
but I am going to find it.
如果我不能 再替宇宙其它的分心
If I have to tear another black hole,
是因为我要去找它
I'm going to find it!
我必须如此
I've got to, mister!
好极了
Oh, great!
我会出去阻止他们过来
I'll try to head them off.
快出来吧
Ace, get out of the tank.
不行 队长
I just can't do it, captain!
我已没能量了
I don't have the power!
你马上出来吧
I said, get out of the tank now!
我只是个医生 不是洗池工人
For God's sake, Jim, I'm a doctor, not a pool man!
I'm a doctor, not a pool man!
雪花在何处？
Where's Snowflake?
暂时不能与大家见面
Snowflake is not available right now.
我都等了一整天了
Roger, I've been waiting all day.
我一定要拍到它的新闻
I got to get a shot of his new trick!
它是否病了？
What, is he sick?
拉茜一定是失踪了
Lassie must be missing.
喂！威龙
Hey, Ventura.
最近有否侦破大案件？
Make any good collars lately?
还扔是普通案件？
Or were they leashes?
谋杀案 威龙
Homicide, Ventura.
你打算如何侦破此案？
How are you gonna solve that one?
问得好
Good question, Aguado!
首先 我会先找出犯案动机
First, I'd establish a motive.
这案子 凶手因妒死者老二太大
The killer saw the size of the bug's dick and became insanely jealous.
然后 你会慰籍凶手太太
Then I'd lose 30 pounds porking his wife!
深深一吻 请求原谅
Now, kiss and make up!
对不起 我有问题问你
Excuse me.I'd like to ass you a few questions.
这不是合适的时间
This is not the time, Ace.
如果艾路丝下来看见 我便死定
If Einhorn come down here and see me talking to you or your ass, I'm history.
你必需告诉我雪花一案谁负责
I can keep him under control. You have to tell me who's on the Snowflake case.
我帮不了你 太多限制
I can't do nothing for you on that. My hands are tied.
现在到我问了
All right, that's it! Now it's my turn!
我只需五分钟独处
Five minutes alone, that's all I need!
快装得很忙样子 艾下来了
Better look alive. Einhorn's on her way down.
快点 求求你
Come on, now. Ace, please.
什么事 怕我放屁吗？
What's that matter? Afraid I'll make a stink? Come on!
阿瓜多负责那案的 这下行了吧？
Aguado's working the case, all right?
阿瓜多
Aguado!
说的好
Good call!
看 我们现在很忙！
We're just a little busy now…
有命案 劫案和毒犯要应付
with murderers and burglaries and drug dealers. Things like that.
海豚失踪不算是大案
A missing dolphin isn't exactly a high priority.
现在你令他生气了
Now you've pissed him off.
你饶了我…
Would you give me a break?
我无法再控制他
I can't hold him much longer!
我上司来了
My boss is coming!
好吧
Okay, look.
我们已查过动物权益组织
We ran a check with local animal-rights groups.
也查过标本店和租车公司
We checked out the taxidermists and we already checked on van rentals.
到目前为止 仍没有线索
So far, nothing, nathin', nada. All right?
有没有不寻常的外围投注？
Any unusual bets being made?
当然有 这是超级杯嘛！
Of course! This is Super Bowl!
在那水池有何发现？
What'd you find out about the tank?
没什么特别的
Nothing.
一些轮迹 逃走路线
Tire tracks, an escape route.
和一个什么也没看见的守卫
A guard didn't see anything.
- 只此而已？- 我看是
- That's it? - I swear.
我发誓 趁我未惹上麻烦
Now will you please get out of here.
请快走
before I get in trouble?
谢谢你的合作 另外…
Thank you for your cooperation.By the way,
你有薄荷糖吗？
do you have a mint?
奸人糖呢？
Perhaps some Binaca?
我的妈！
Holy testicle Tuesday!
他怎会在此的
What the hell is he doing here?
我来自首
I came to confess.
我是刺杀肯尼迪的另一枪手
I was the second gunman on the grassy knoll.
少废话 我知你在查雪花一案
Spare me the routine. I know you're working the Snowflake case.
我建议你把它交由专家处理
May I suggest you yield to the experts on this one?
我们会找到这海猪
We'll find the porpoise.
我深感如释重负
Now I feel better.
当然 那或许无补于事
Of course, that might not do any good.
没人失去海猪 被偷的是海豚
Nobody's missing a porpoise. It's a dolphin that's been taken.
普通海猪是大牙齿
The common harbor porpoise has an abrupt snout…
而长鼻海豚是圆尖齿
while the bottle-nosed dolphin, or Tursiops truncatus…
这是两种截然不同的牙齿
has an elongated beak, cone-shaped teeth and a serrated dorsal appendage.
当然 你已全知道这些
But I'm sure you already knew that.
你令我心动的便是这点
That's what turns me on about you.
你真是观察入微
Your attention to detail.
你听着 宠物鸡巴
Listen, pet dick…
要不要我把你的生活变成炼狱
how would you like me to make your life a living hell?
我并不是真的想和你谈恋爱
Well, I'm not really ready for a relationship, Lois.
但谢谢你提出
But thank you for asking.
或许改天给你电话
Maybe I'll give you a call sometime.
你的电话仍是911？
Your number still 911?
对不起 格雷在吗？
Excuse me. Is Greg here?
谢谢你
Thank you!
密码是什么？
What's the password?
新英格兰鱼汤
New England clam chowder.
汤是红色的还是白色的？
Is that the red or the white?
我忘了…
I can never remember that!
白色
White?
胡士托
Hey, Woodstock!
圣方济 你好吗？
Hey, Saint Francis, how's it going?
很好 谢谢关心 希望你也是
Super, thanks for asking. I hope you're having a lovely day.
是吗？
Do you?
还有假的？
Don't I?
你在做什么？猛丁哥
So what are you up to?
只是看鱼
Just watching the fishies.
看见那些吗？那是挪威捕鲸队
You see those blips? That's a Norwegian whaling fleet.
我发给他们新的方位座标
I'm sending them new directional coordinates.
他们一定会找到屈原
They'll find Jimmy Hoffa…before they find any whales.
妙 你可否进入…
Gravy! So can you still tap into.
海洋物品买卖资料库？
the aquatic supply stores in the area?
当然可以 什么事？
Of course I can. Why?
查看近日…
I wanna trace the sale of.
购入运送海豚装置记录
equipment for transporting or housing a dolphin recently.
我还以为有什么挑战
Come on, I thought you had a challenge for me.
海洋绳索 二万加仑的大鱼缸
All right, we got marine winch, sling, feeder fish, 20, 000-gallon tank…
等等 你看
Wait a minute. Look here.
对一个平民来说 真不简单
That's a lot of equipment for a civilian.
哇！可是个百万富翁
Ronald Camp? The billionaire?
亦是罕有鱼类收藏家
Billionaire and rare-fish collector.
真的吗？
Really?
那便是敌人真面目
That is the face of the enemy.
老想染指濒临绝种生物
Always trying to get his greedy hands on endangered species.
等等 他与海豚队有关连？
Hold on.Camp is connected with the dolphins?
是啊 天才 捐地建球场
That subgenius gave them the land the stadium's built on.
看 他又举行「出风头」派对了
And look, he's throwing another "I'm the richest man in the universe" party.
似乎是找个舞伴的时候了
Looks like it's time for me to get myself a date.
我这次可算是冒大险了
I'm really going out on a limb here.
甘氏派对请的全是名流
His social events are strictly A-list.
约会开始时搞得很好了
The date started good, Chuck,
但抵达派对前她脚软
but before we got to the party, she tensed up.
如果你给我带来麻烦…
If you do anything to embarrass me…
什么 像这样？
What? Like this?
嗨 史塔宾队长 霍华和德好吗？
Hi, Captain Stubing.How are Gopher and Doc?
我请求登舰
Permission to come aboard, sir.
失陪一下
I'm sorry, ladies.
玛莉莎
Marisa.
嗨！朗恩
Hey! Ron.
很高兴你能来
Glad you could make it.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 你很美 - 谢谢
- You look wonderful. - Thanks.
他是谁？你朋友？
And who is he, a friend?
不 是我的…我的舞伴
No, this is… This is my date.
他是个律师
He's a lawyer.
他有名字的吗？还是要我叫他「律师先生」
Does he have a name, or should I call him "Lawyer"?
对不起 他叫…王牌…
I'm sorry. This is Ace V…
汤姆·王牌…
Tom Ace.
幸会 也恭贺你今晚的成功
Pleasure to meet you.Congratulations on all your success.
你的气味真是一流
You smell terrific!
我才刚和玛莉莎说我们在大学就有一门…
One of the first lessons we learned back at…
专门研究食物毒害富人官司的
Stanford was the growth of food- poisoning claims against wealthy-people.
只这一门就可以开专门律师行
One could make quite a lucrative law practice with little else.
今晚每个人觉得如何？
How is everybody feeling tonight?
非常 非常好 谢谢你
Very, very well, thank you.
甜心 那儿有法式小点
Look, honey…there's the hors d'oeuvres.
回头见
See you.
你疯了吗？雪花不会是甘偷的
Are you insane? There is no way that Camp stole Snowflake.
你想怎样？
What are you trying to do?
我行动前想法缠着他
Will you keep him occupied while I work my magic, please?
很好吃 是不是？
Smooshy, isn't it?
巴黎酒店送了数箱给我
We got a few cases from my new dealer in Paris.
对不起
Excuse me, Ron…
我要上厕所
I need to use the bathroom.
一定是那些肝酱作怪
I think it's the paste?
- 厕所在那边 - 谢谢
- Sure, it's over there.- Thanks.
这东西出来时定比进去时好看
Stuff probably looks better on the way out.
他老早就已不大舒服了
He wasn't feeling well earlier today.
好极了
Gravy!
放心吧 雪花
Don't worry, Snowflake.
威龙来了
Ace Ventura's here.
好吃喔！
Yummy!
雪花
Snowflake!
Here, Snowflake.
我有东西给你吃
I've got a snack for you.
这些鱼美丽吗？
They're wonderful, aren't they?
十分美丽
Yes, they certainly are.
无论我遇上什么挫折…
No matter what's going on in my life…
看见它们便觉心平气和
I can always watch them swim and be totally at peace.
这不是雪花！这不是雪花
It's not Snowflake!It's not Snowflake!
你的朋友不会有事吧？
Are you sure your date is all right?
他已去了很久
It's been an awfully long time.
你说汤姆
Who, Tom?
他不会有事的
Well, I'm sure he's fine.
别进去那里
Do not go in there!
对不起 我马上找水管匠来
I'm sorry. I'll have the plumbing checked immediately.
快 如果我喝了那厕所水便没命
Do that! If I'd been drinking out of the toilet, I might've been killed.
对不起 王牌先生
I'm sorry again, Mr. Ace.
你做什么？
What're you doing?
很抱歉
I'm sorry, Ron.
- 他做什么？- 我们走吧
- What's he doing? - Let's go!
停止
Stop it!
我真不明白你的裤子去了哪里
I don't even wanna know why your pants are missing!
你可能令我失业的
You could've cost me my job!
原来你在雪花的水池找到石子 我马上打电话CNN
So you found a pebble in Snowflake's tank. I'll call CNN.
在水池找到的
I found it in the filter, thank you.
这不是石子 是罕有的橙宝石
And it's not a pebble, it's a rare, triangular cut orange amber.
你在说什么？
What're you talking about?
我今晚 见甘的戒指…
Tonight I saw the same stone.
镶有同样宝石
in Camp's ring.
你说过雪花不是他偷的
I thought you said Camp didn't do it.
对 他戒指上的宝石仍在
No, his ring wasn't missing a stone.
偷海豚的人一定有同样的戒指
But whoever was in that tank had a ring just like his.
什么戒指？
Ring? What ring?
84年海豚队美国联盟冠军戒指
The 1984 Dolphin AFC championship ring.
找到那戒指之人便可找到雪花
I find the ring with a missing stone, I find Snowflake.
你打算怎样做？
How you gonna do that?
很简单
Simple.
失败者
Loser!
你为何不学好驾驶？
Why don't you learn how to drive, pal?
你想玩玩吗？
You wanna play?
妈的
Damn it!
那宝石可能来自任何地方的
That stone could've come from anywhere.
可能来自项链或耳环
It could've come from a necklace or a pendant, an earring.
那是84年美国联盟冠军戒指上
It came from an '84 AFC championship ring.
艾路丝组长认为是动物权益组
Einhorn thinks it may have been an animal-rights group.
你听过FAN吗？
You know FAN?
富女简秋霞发起的解放动物会
Free Animals Now, started by Chelsea, daughter of industrialist Fisher Gamble?
全球有超过五十万会员
Over half a million members worldwide?
没听过 他们是什么人？
No. Who are they?
他们去年发出127封恐吓信
Did you know…
要求各队放生吉祥物
they sent letters to college teams demanding the release of their mascots?
你用什么喂狗的？
What do you feed your dog?
狗粮 什么事？
Dog food. Why?
他很可怜
He is miserable!
你到底在说什么？
What are you talking about?
它很不快乐 我为它难过
He's very unhappy. I feel sorry for him.
伙食差 与世隔绝
Bad diet, isolated environment.
奇怪的是它还活着
It's amazing he's still alive.
你的宝石原理行不通所以生气
You're just mad because your stupid pebble theory didn't work out.
你的愤怒难以宣泄
You can't express anger.
是吗？你很丑陋
Yeah? And you're ugly.
我甚至不想和你谈话 走吧！
I'm not even gonna talk to you. Would you please leave?
为什么？让你可以打它？
Why? So you can beat him?
肥妹
Fatty!
你真离谱
You're unbelievable!
聘用你是个大错
Hiring you was the biggest mistake I ever made.
你何不大哭一场？大屁股
Well, why don't you cry about it, saddlebags?
你喜欢她？
You like her, huh?
是的 她很不错
Yeah, she's all right.
听好 我…
Look, Melissa, I…
我在北峰大厦外…
I'm here at the North Beach Towers condo complex in north Miami…
海豚队领队普罗杰自杀的现场
where Roger Podacter, head of operations for the Miami Dolphins has apparently committed suicide…
据说是从二十多楼跳下…
allegedly leaping to his death from his 20th-story balcony…
你没事吧？
You okay?
我已说过 当时我在家中
I told you. I was in my apartment across the hall.
我听到尖叫
I heard a scream…
于是通知大厦经理
so I called the manager.
那儿除了狗 什么也没有
The place was empty, except for the dog.
我打开阳台我们看出去…
I opened the balcony door and looked out…
便见那一滩血饼
splat, bang, pancake time.
非常谢谢
Okay, thank you very much.
今晚很不安 是吗？
Have a bad night?
动物能嗅到邪恶的事物
So animals can sense evil.
谁让这兽医进来的
Who let Dr. Doolittle in?
他跟麦小姐一起到的
Lieutenant, he came with Miss Robinson.
这是警方的事
This is police business.
验尸时找到血及虫才通知你
We'll let you know if the coroner finds a tick.
面对现实吧
Face it…
不 她是对的 而且…
Forget it. She's right.Besides…
我也不想人指出我的错误
I wouldn't want someone tracing my steps, pointing out my mistakes.
你不认为这是自杀案
So…you don't think this is an obvious suicide, Mr. Pet Detective?
我没那样说
I wouldn't say that.
因没有证据支持这观点
There's plenty of evidence here to support your theory.
除了 那扶手上的血渍
Except, of course, for that spot of blood on the railing.
能告诉你我的想法吗？
May I tell you what I think happened?
普罗杰下班后喝过几杯便回家
Roger Podacter went out after work, had a few drinks, then came home.
但他不是单独一人
He wasn't alone.
后来他们发生争执 他被人扔下阳台
Someone else was with him. There was a struggle…and he was thrown over that balcony.
普罗杰不是自杀 是被谋杀
Roger Podacter didn't commit suicide.He was murdered.
这真是个很有趣的故事
That's a very entertaining story…
但真正侦探一切讲求证据
but real detectives have to worry about that little thing called evidence.
我听到有人冲厕所
I think I heard a toilet flush.
或者有海龟已走失了
Maybe somebody lost a turtle.
看来我已技穷
Well, I…I guess I'm out of my league here.
做得好
Good work.
还有一件事 队长
There is just one more thing, lieutenant.
这女人住在对面单位的
This woman is Roger Podacter's neighbor.
她说听到尖叫声 是吗？
She said she heard a scream. Right?
没错
Right.
而你说进来时要打开阳台的门
And you had to open the balcony door when you came in?
- 那是真的 - 你肯定要打开这门？
- That's true. - You're sure you had to open this door?
是的
I'm certain.
你想证明什么？威龙
What's the point, Ventura?
只想证明一件事
Only this.
这是双重隔音玻璃
This is double-paned, soundproof glass. There is no way…
邻居是无法听到普的尖叫声
she could have heard Podacter scream on the way down.
她听到的尖叫是来自这室内
The scream she heard came from inside…
他被扔出阳台之后
before he was thrown off the balcony.
凶手离开前关上这门
The murderer closed the door upon going.
明白吗？
Can you feel that, buddy?
我已驱走恶魔
I have exorcized the demons!
这屋子安全了
This house is clear.
- 全是失败者 - 赶他出去
- Losers. - Get him out of here!
回动物园去吧
Back to the zoo.
你在想什么？
What are you thinking?
整件事与雪花被盗有关连
This whole thing is connected, somehow.
我要找到那戒指
I want to find that other ring.
你已查过所有的戒指
Ace, you checked all the rings.
收据呢？
Receipts? What about receipts?
一定有的
There's gotta be receipts.
（1990年足总物资）
你刚才的表现很出色
That was pretty impressive, what you did at the apartment.
你无需告诉我
You don't have to tell me.
我很了解自己
I was there.
或者你该做个真正的侦探
Maybe you should've joined the police force, become a real detective.
我不做与人类有关的案件
I don't do humans.
你真的很爱动物
You really love animals.
如果天气够冷的话
If it gets cold enough.
不 其实和他们有亲戚关系
No, I have a kinship with them.
我了解它们
I understand them.
是否要听怪异故事？
Wanna hear something spooky?
我十二岁那年做了个梦
One time when I was about 12, I had a dream that I was being followed by…
我被一只疯狗跟着
a big dog with rabies.
他双眼血红 口吐白沫
He had these bloodshot eyes…and foam came out of his mouth.
无论我跑多快 它也越来越近
No matter how fast I ran, he just kept gaining on me and gaining on me.
就在我走进家门前
Then just before I got to my front door…
他跳了过来 咬着我
he jumped and sank his teeth in.
我醒了后 摸摸颈背
That's when I woke up…and felt the back of my neck. Check that out.
你看看
you check out.
狗杂种
Bastard!
对不起 我情不自禁
I'm sorry, I just couldn't help myself.
知道我为何干这行吗？
Want to know why I do this?
我也不知道想不想
I'm not sure anymore.
你最好知道…
You better be sure…
因为你一旦了解我…
because once you get inside my head…
便不会以我表面的作为来判断
there's no turning back.
是否全部收据都在此了？
Are these all? There's only a dozen.
或许在后面另一档案内吧
Maybe it's in another file, in the back.
- 那是谁？- 什么
- Who the hell is that? - What?
他是谁？
Who the hell is that?
雷费高 踢球员 你不认识他
That's Ray Finkle, the kicker. Don't you know who he is?
他为何不在这照片中
Why isn't he in this picture?
这是较早前拍的
This was taken earlier in the year.
他在季中才加入
Ray Finkle wasn't added till mid-season.
那年他踢失了决定性的一球
He missed the final field goal in the Super Bowl that year.
令海豚队得不到冠军
Cost the Dolphins the game.
但他有戒指 是吗？
But he got himself a ring, didn't he?
当然了
Definitely.
新踢球员带来丰盛的一年
"Replacement kicker having a great year."
明星踢球员扬言进军超级杯
"Ready for Super Bowl, all-star kicker boasts."
临门脚软 冠军泡汤
"Field goal sails wide, Dolphins lose Super Bowl."
名闻天下的一脚
"The kick heard round the world."
全是说费高的
That was Finkle.
海豚队以一分输了
The Dolphins lost by one point.
（费高不获续约）
可怜的傢伙
Poor guy.
他有犯案动机
Poor guy with a motive, baby.
他现在何处？
Where is he now?
回了家乡古利镇
I heard he went back to his hometown in Collier County.
真的
Really?
你在起程前会送我回家吧
You're gonna drop me off before you go?
不 目前你不宜独居
No way. You shouldn't be left alone right now.
你的家已不是安全之地
It might not be safe at your apartment.
你有何建议？
What do you suggest?
我的天…
Oh, my God!
我们已做了三次！
Three times?
对不起 以前我未试过不行的
I'm sorry, that's never happened to me before.
我一定是太累了
I must be tired.
我又可以了
Okay, I'm ready again.
（古利镇 雷费狗的家乡）
（废狗 不会踢球的笨蛋）
（笨蛋…）
（费高烂货）
我想找雷费高…
I'm looking for Ray Finkle…
和一条新的内裤
and a clean pair of shorts.
你对他有何认识？
What do you know about Ray Finkle?
足球踢球员 七六年高中毕业
Soccer-style kicker. Graduated from Collier High, 1976.
80年大学毕业
Stetson University honors graduate, 1980.
拥有两项NCAA记录
Holds two NCAA records.
得分最多 踢得最远
Most points and distance.
以前绰号叫马子
Nickname, "The Mule."
此地的唯一职业运动员
The only pro athlete from here.
也是美国人模范之一
And one hell of a model American.
你又是新闻特写记者？
Are you another one of them Hard Copy guys?
不 只是他的球迷
No, sir.I'm just a big Finkle fan.
这儿是我的圣地
This is my Graceland, sir.
放下枪！
Will you put that gun down?
他只是个球迷
The boy is a fan of our son.
幸会 我是费高的母亲
So nice to meet you.I'm Ray's mother…
这是他父亲
and this is Ray's father.
我深感荣幸
It's a real honor!
有你的光临才是荣幸
It's an honor to have you here.
我儿子很喜欢他的球迷
My Ray is so appreciative of his fans.
他会很高兴你来探他
He'll be so pleased you stopped by.
你说他随时会回来？
Are you expecting Ray anytime soon?
是的 他随时回来的
Oh, yes. I expect him home any minute.
要吃饼吗？刚做好的
Would you like some cookies? I just baked them.
好啊
Yummy!
雷费高之家
Ray Finkle's house.
我迫不及待想见他
I can't wait to meet him.
他不会回来的
Ray ain't coming home.
你太太说他随时会回来
But your wife expects him any minute.
她无时无刻不在等他
She expects him home any minute.
明白吗？他是失控列车
See, the engine's running but there's nobody behind the wheel.
八年前
Eight years ago…
我们儿子从精神院逃了出来
our son escaped from Shady Acres Mental Hospital.
他们仍在叫我拿回他的衣物
And they're still bugging us to pick up his stuff.
那是马理诺的错 人人皆知
It was all that Dan Marino's fault. Everyone knows that.
如果他持球时把车缝口向外
If he'd held the ball laces out, like he's supposed to…
费高便不会踢失那球
Ray wouldn't have missed the kick.
马理诺该生梅毒死去
Dan Marino should die of gonorrhea.
万劫不复
and rot in hell.
要吃饼吗？
Would you like a cookie, son?
我的天…全是小足球
What do you know?They're little footballs.
缝口向外
Laces out.
等费高回来 再踢足球
When Ray gets back and starts kicking again…
他甚至不会发觉他离开过
he'll never even know he was gone.
他的房跟他离开时一样
I've kept his room just the way he left it.
（缝口向外 死马理诺）
（马理诺13号）
哇！真狠
Oh, boy!
体育狂 是吗？
What a sports nut, huh?
- 可以吗？- 请随便
- May I? - Oh, yes, by all means.
十七届超级杯还有五秒便完场
Five seconds to go here in Super Bowl 17.
海豚队只落后49人队一分
Dolphins trailing the 49ers…
这球将可助迈哈密取胜
by one. This will win the game for Miami.
马理诺负责持球 踢出
Marino holds.The kick…
球飞得很高…
and it's high.
不 过门不入
No, it's…no good.
雷费高临门失机
Ray Finkle blew a 26-yard field goal!
令人无法相信
I don 't believe it!
海豚队输了…
The Dolphins lose!
The Dolphins lose! The Dolphins lose the Super Bowl!
- 玛莉莎是我 - 你在哪？
- Melissa, it's Ace! - Where are you?
我在疯人村 马理诺在哪？
I'm in psychoville, and Finkle's the mayor. Where's Marino?
马理诺 为什么？
Why?
他可能和雪花一起
He's about to join Snowflake.
我必需知道他在那里
I've gotta know where he is!
他去了保加片场拍广告
He has a commercial shoot at the Bogart Sound Stage.
快报警 并加派保安进去
Call the police. Get extra security over there. Now!
怎么回事？王牌！王牌
Ace, what's going on?
以为我走了吗？
Thought I left?
这次我真的走了
I'm really gonna go this time.
大家安静 开始
Here we go, folks. Very quiet.Action!
我是唐马理诺 深明保护之道
I'm Dan Marino, and if anyone knows the value of protection, it's me.
所以我照顾这双手
So I take care of the hands that take care of me…
采用伊苏东拿手套
with lsotoner gloves!
停止 从头再来
Cut! Again from the top.
- 我说停下来 - 停下来
- I said, cut! - Guys, it's a cut!
他们做什么？
What the hell are they doing?
我们叫停止
That's a cut!
- 什么事 又改剧本吗？- 闭嘴
- What is this, a rewrite? - Shut up!
- 他们去那儿了？- 那边 走
- Where'd they go? - Over there!Let's go!
对不起 各位
Excuse me, gentlemen!
宠物侦探来了
Pet detective!
你怎么了 打不中我的？
What's wrong?Can't you hit me?
他们有否要求赎金
Have there been ransom demands?
绑匪尚未跟我们联络
There's no communication with the kidnappers.
超级杯是否会延期举行？
Will the Super Bowl be postponed?
球赛如期举行
The game is on as scheduled.
为何没有雪花的消息公布
Why weren't we told about the kidnapping?
为了保密理由
Secrecy was essential. We couldn't risk any interference.
两案是否有关连？
Are the crimes related?
对不起 暂无进一步评论
I'm sorry, I can't comment further.
失陪
Now, if you'll excuse me…
拿普罗杰的验尸报告出来
Get me the autopsy on Podacter!
阿瓜多 发张通告
Aguado, send out a memo.
谁也不准向新闻界发表谈话
No one talks to the press!
拿杯咖啡给我
And somebody get me some coffee!
今晚的罪恶克星
Tonight on Miami Vice,
高杰给上司送咖啡
Crockett gets the boss a coffee!
我从洗手间出来前
When I get out of that bathroom,
你最好消失
you'd better be gone!
你是大便还是小便？
Is it number one or number two?
我想知道有多少时间
I just wanna know how much time I have.
无论如何我已解开…
By the way, I went ahead and solved that…
雪花 普罗杰和马理诺之谜
pesky Snowflake-Podacter-Marino thing.
- 是吗？- 是啊
- Oh yeah? - Yeah.
你听说过雷费高这踢球员吗？
You ever heard of a former Dolphin kicker named Ray Finkle?
好吧 长话短说！
All right, Ventura…make it quick.
我在雪花的池内找到一个宝石
I found a rare stone at the bottom of Snowflake's tank.
是84年美国联盟冠军戒指上的
It belongs to a Dolphin '84 AFC championship ring.
那年费高踢失一球
It would've been a Super Bowl ring,
输掉超级杯
but Ray missed the kick.
把责任推在马理诺身上
Blames the whole thing on Marino.
我们说的是个疯子
We're talking paranoid, delusional psychosis.
我看过这人的房间
I saw the guy's room.
如果你是吃人狂的话 会住得很舒适
Cozy, if you're Hannibal Lecter.
与普罗杰又何关？
So how does Roger Podacter fit in?
我相信费高被普认出
My guess is, Finkle was snooping around. Podacter recognized him. End of story.
至于雪花 他用了费高的号码
As for Snowflake, they gave him Finkle's number,
并学他踢球
taught him how to kick a goal.
费高认为是耻辱
Finkle took it personally.
费高现在何处？
So where is Finkle now?
逃离疯人院
Busted out of a mental institute.
他已计划这次行动多年
He's been plotting his revenge for years.
等待时机向海豚队报复
Waiting for the perfect time to get back at them.
最能打击海豚队的时刻
The time when it'd hurt them most:
是超级杯赛
Super Bowl time.
老天 我已对正确生厌了
Man, I'm tired of being right!
恭喜你
Congratulations.
你做得很好…
You've done some fine detective work…
王牌…
Ace…
对不起 请向着我未聋的耳说
I'm sorry, could you speak into my good ear?
你似乎叫我王牌
I thought I heard you call me Ace.
或许我以前看错你了
Maybe I was wrong about you.
或者你不只是个宠物鸡巴
Maybe you are more than just a pet dick.
你的枪压住我了
Your gun is digging into my hip.
什么事？要否我宣独你的权利
What's wrong?Want me to read you your rights?
或者迟些吧
Maybe later.
究竟是什么事？
What is it?
那瘦骨婊子…玛莉莎？
That bony little bitch…Melissa Robinson?
你不会让我感到触电吧！
You just don't do anything for me.
趴下
Down, boy!
没事吧 我听到声音
Everything okay in here? I heard some commotion.
没事
Fine, sergeant.
要否我赶他走？
You want me to throw him out?
你何不自己滚出去？
Why don't you throw yourself out?
是的
Yes, ma'am.
王牌 把一切交给我们处理
Ace, I want you to leave everything to us.
不行 我受聘找寻雪花
I can't do that, lieutenant. I was hired to find Snowflake.
我们找到马理诺
When we find Marino…
便把雪花给你
we'll deliver Snowflake.
我找到雪花 把马理诺给你
When I find Snowflake…I'll deliver Marino.
玛莉莎 是我
Melissa, it's Ace!
你来此干吗？半夜三更的
What are you doing here? It's the middle of the night.
你必需弄我进疯人院
You have to commit me.
费高逃离后 仍有衣物在院中
Finkle escaped from Shady Acres. They still have his stuff.
他们不会准我们四处看的
They aren't gonna let us look around.
我知道 幸好我是伪装专家
I know.It's a good thing I'm a master of disguise.
罗宾森小姐 我是韩医生
Mrs. Robinson…I'm Dr. Handly.
你想要我们看谁？
Now who is it you want us to look at?
我哥哥 拉利
My brother…Larry.
教练 我已很好 让我出场吧
I'm ready to go in. Just give me a chance!
我知道这比赛很重要
I know there's a lot riding on it.
但那是心理问题 向正面想
But it's all psychological.Just gotta stay positive.
我会施展战术…慢动作
I'm gonna execute a buttonhook pattern, super slow-mo.
现在即时重播
Let's see that in an instant replay.
他不是这儿第一个足球员
Your brother won't be the first football pro we've treated.
- 是吗 - 是的
- Is that right? - Yes.
我们很关注运动员所受的压力
We're very sensitive…to the stress athletes have to endure.
我在空位！没人防守！
I'm open! I'm open!I'm open!
我们会作初步评估的
We'll do some preliminary evaluations…
我相信他在此会很好的
but I think he'll fit in nicely here.
这儿…
Over here!
351！
351!
他似乎无法忘记那比赛
He seems to have some difficulty letting go of the game.
他有精神病记录吗？
Has he had a history of mental illness?
自我认识他便有
As long as I've known him.
这是我们的一间治疗室
This is one of our therapy rooms.
我们会在这儿做手工艺
And we do arts and crafts out here in the courtyard.
这是储物室 再下去还有…
And this is the storage room. Down the hallway we have another…
半场
Halftime!
廿分钟内他不会有事的
He'll be fine there by himself for the next 20 minutes.
我带你去看看宿舍
I'll show you the dormitories, then.
费高
Finkle.
伊苏东拿手套
Isotoners.
（去死 马理诺）
（缝口向外）
死心眼
Obsess much?
- 你去那儿？- 清洁储物室
- Where are you going? - To clean the storage room.
不 先清洁小吃部
No, clean the cafeteria.
我不知如何告诉你…去吧
I don't tell you how to do your job.The schedule says…
我知自己做什么的
I know what I'm doing.
你该老早就已洗洁好它
You should've done it earlier.
去吧 我清洁这儿
Man, come on. Cafeteria, my ass! I'm cleaning in here!
你休息得太久了
You take breaks too long. You smoke…
你真讨厌
Man, you're a pain in the ass!
搜索失踪旅行者的行动已终止
"Search called off for missing hiker."
拯救者无法找到艾露丝的尸体
"A search ended today when rescue workers…
搜索行动今天结束
were unable to find the body of Lois Einhorn."
旅行者失踪？艾露丝
A hiker missing since Friday?Lois Einhorn?
我的天
Holy shitballs!
你们在做什么？回去工作
What're you doing out here? Get back to work!
（亲爱的露丝 谢谢赐与良宵…）
（爱你的罗杰？）
"Love, Roger?"
王牌 是我
Ace, it's E.
你以为你的发现很重要吗？
You think the article you found was something?
我找到张普送给艾的纸条
I got a note from Roger to Einhorn…
感谢她赐与良宵
thanking her for a wonderful evening.
此事很不对劲
Something ain 't stirring the Kool-Aid, man.
摇尾 倒带
Wiggles, rewind.
艾路丝和雷费高有何关连？
What the hell does Lois Einhorn have to do with Ray Finkle?
想吧！
Come on, think!
雷和艾同谋此事？为什么？
Finkle and Einhorn, in it together. How? Why?
答案就在那儿 用用脑吧
All right! Here we go.Answer's right there! Just gotta get blood to the brain!
雷费高和艾露丝…
Finkle and Einhorn! Finkle and Einhorn!
我得努力想…
Finkle and Einhorn!
费高和艾露丝
懒鬼
Quitter!
你想要什么？
What do you want?
我已没食物
I don't have any food for you.
要买食物必需有钱
I have to have money to buy food.
要有钱必需有海豚
I have to have a dolphin to get money.
你看见这儿有海豚吗？
Do you see a dolphin here?
面对现实吧 你主人是失败者
Let's face it…your master is a loser.
等等…
What the…
对了…
That's it.
艾就是雷费高 雷费高就是艾
Einhorn is Finkle.Finkle is Einhorn!
艾露丝是个男人
Einhorn is a man!
我的天 艾露丝是个男人
Oh, my God!Einhorn is a man!
你的枪压住我了
"Your gun is digging into my hip."
老天
God!
这次超级杯的头条是…
And the big story in this Super Bowl game is the abduction…
海豚队的马理诺被俘虏
of Miami's starting quarterback, Dan Marino.
这对该队一定构成影响
It's gotta be a strain on this Miami team, Bob…
什么事？你不开心？
What's the matter, Dan? Aren't you having fun?
我最爱周日的超级杯 你呢？
I just love Super Bowl Sunday. Don't you, Dan?
一个奇妙的下午…
A magical afternoon…
也是梦想形成和粉碎的场合
where dreams are made and crushed.
拜托 小姐
Look.
如果你想找球票 找错地方了
if you want tickets, you're going about it the wrong way.
我看来面熟吗？
Do I look familiar to you? Does it seem as if we've…
我们是否见过面？
met someplace before?
我不知道
I don't know.
我头部常受到撞击的
I get hit in the head a lot.
现在该丢钱了 开赛
Now the coin toss.Kickoff time.
我最爱看开球的
My favorite thing.
缝口向外
Laces out!
我做了些点心
I made some refreshments, Dan.
你要吗？
Would you like some refreshments, Dan?
我马上便回来
I'll be right back, Dan.
那一吻可真野啊！
This is wild.
喂！兄弟
Hey, guys!
那疯妇给你多少 我付双倍的
I don't know how much psycho-woman's paying you, but I'll double it.
对不起 疯妇免我们坐牢
Sorry."Psycho-woman" keeps us out of prison.
雪花
Snowflake, here you go. Come on.
你看 我把球传给雪花
Check it out, Marino.I'm throwing passes to a dolphin.
多拿点鱼来
Go get some more fish!
我该杀了它
I'm gonna kill that dolphin.
好热闹的派对 可惜我没被邀
Lovely party.Pity I wasn't invited.
银鱼在何处？
Where the hell's the smelt?
不省人事…一如我计划的
Unconscious. Exactly as I planned.
什么声音？
What the hell was that?
该死
Shit!
发生什么事？你没事吧？
What happened? What's going on?You okay?
午睡时间
Guess what?It's naptime!
太糟了 球被拦下来…
What a hit!
喂！你们
Heads up!
嗨！唐
Hi!Dan.
你是谁？
Who are you?
宠物侦探王牌威龙…因特别任务而来
Ace Ventura, Pet Detective. I've been sent with a special play:
释放四分卫
The quarterback sneak.
罚球
Penalty!
场中人数太多
Too many men on the field.
我已警告过你的 威龙
I warned you, Ventura.
不是王牌哥了？
Whatever happened to "Ace"?
问得好
Good question.
小心用那电话 会死人的
Be careful with that phone. In time, you could develop a tumor.
阿瓜多 我是艾露丝队长
Aguado, it's Lieutenant Einhorn.
派人来荷兰游艇会
Send some men over to the Hallandale yacht basin.
我已把绑匪困在货仓内
I've got the kidnapper trapped in the warehouse.
是宠物侦探威龙
It's Ace Ventura, Pet Detective.
拘捕绑匪行动进行中
Code 11 in progress, 343 Victorville Road at the Palmdale basin.
有警官需支援
Officer needs backup.
疑犯名叫威龙…
Suspect's name: Ace Ventura…
是有枪的危险人物
should be considered armed and dangerous.
是威龙 我们快赶去
It's Ace. We gotta break out of here.
他有麻烦？
Is he in trouble?
别担心 我只知道…
Don't worry, if there's one thing I know…
他没有不能应付的事
there's nothing Ace can't handle.
别杀我
Don't kill me!
求求你
Please!
我发誓不会告诉任何人
I'll never tell anyone, I swear.
你要的是他 杀他吧
He's who you want! Kill him!
- 不 先杀他 - 杀他才对
- Kill him! - Kill him!
记住 持球的是他？
He held the ball, remember?
你看他
Come on, look at him!
- 该哭了 宝贝 - 小人
- Crybaby! - Jock! Wimp.
- 白痴 - 闭嘴
- Musclehead. - Shut up!
我会先杀那海豚 我不想你错过
I think I'll kill the dolphin first. I wouldn't want you to miss that.
射门了 一矢中的
And there's the snap.The kick!And it's good!
幸好他没临门脚软
Good to see somebody who doesn't buckle under the pressure!
你对压力有何认识
What would you know about pressure?
我吻过一个男人
Well, I have kissed a man.
当然超级杯历史上…
Of course, there's never been a more crucial kick in a.
没有比雷费高那次…
Super Bow lthan the "kick heard around the world."
更令人印象深刻的了
I mean, it's clear to me that it was a good hold. Finkle just booted it.
当时缝口向内的
The laces were in!
你喜欢这样？
You like that?
对付那女人有麻烦吗？
Having a little trouble with the lady?
你不明白 她不是…
You don't understand…she's a…
揍他 露丝
Get him, Lois! Get him!Get him!
开枪射他！
Shoot him!
- 开枪！- 别开枪
- Shoot him! - Hold your fire!
别开枪
Don't shoot!
放下枪 否则他没命
Put your guns down, or this cop gets it!
我是认真的
I mean it!
她不是说笑的
She's not joking!
他偷走了雪花
He kidnapped Snowflake!
他杀了普罗杰
He killed Roger Podacter.
而且企图杀马理诺和我
and was about to kill Marino and me!
虚构也是乐事
Fiction can be fun!
但我认为事实更有启发性
But I find the reference section much more enlightening.
举例说…
For instance…
如果你翻查职业足球的百科全书
if you look up professional football's all-time bonehead plays…
最差的射门可能是雷费高
you might read about a Miami Dolphin kicker named Ray Finkle…
在十七届射失的那一球
who missed a 26-yard field goal in the closing seconds of Super Bowl 17.
但你不会知他后来进疯人院
You wouldn't read that Finkle was committed to a mental hospital…
逃了出来 借失踪女人的身份
only to escape and join the police…
在警界扶摇直上
in a scheme to get even with Marino…
并策划向马理诺报复
whom he blamed for the entire thing!
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
她不是艾露丝 是雷费高 是个男人
She's not Lois Einhorn! She's Ray Finkle! She's a man!
他说谎
He's lying!
杀了他
Shoot him!
且看是谁在说谎吧
Let's just see who's lying, shall we?
真正女人会戴这个吗？
Would a real woman have to wear one of these?
老天 原来是真发
Boy, that's really on there!
那来看看这个
But tell me this:
真正的女人会没胸的吗？
Would a real woman be missing these?
做这种手术只需数天
That kind of surgery can be done over the weekend.
但是 我很想知道
But I doubt very much…
她能否抽出时间…
if he could find the time during his busy schedule…
去切除他的…子孙根
to get rid of big old…Mr. Knish!
天啊
Oh, boy!
王牌 你过来
Come here.
失陪一会儿
Would you excuse me for just one second?
各位 我的同僚马理诺先生
Ladies and gentlemen…my esteemed colleague, Mr. Marino…
给了我新的启示
brought new evidence to my attention.
历史证明 许多最能干的侦探
Now…history has certainly shown that even the most intuitive…
中间也会出错
criminal investigator can be wrong.
但如果是我弄错了…
But if I am mistaken…
如果艾警长真的是女人
if the lieutenant is indeed a woman as she claims to be…
那么 她定是患了最大的痔疮
then, my friend…she is suffering from the worst case of hemorrhoids I have ever seen!
这便是普罗杰死的原因
That's why Roger Podacter is dead!
他发现了「大棍」警长
He found Captain Winkie!
各位晚安 你们是难得的观众
Good night!You've been a wonderful audience.
记住给侍者付小费
Be sure to tip your waitress.
去死吧
Die, animal boy!
当机立断
Quick decision.
失败者
Loser!
有口香糖吗？
You have any more gum?
不关你事 别管我的私事
That's none of your damn business. Stay out of my personal affairs.
你真了不起 真了不起
You're a weird guy, Ace. A weird guy.
各位 海豚队深感荣幸
Ladies and gentlemen…the Miami Dolphins are proud…
可得回我们的吉祥物…
to welcome back to Joe Robbie Stadium our beloved mascot…
及半场的表现名星…雪花
and the star of our halftime show: Snowflake!
及在下半场入场的…
And now returning for the second half, the Dolphins most valuable player…
唐马理诺
Dan Marino!
- 笨蛋 - 什么事？
- Idiot! - What?
知道你刚做了什么？
Do you know what you've done?
你让我损失了二万五千元
You just cost me 25 grand, Polly.
打我呀！
Yeah? Blow me!
真的
Really?
足总希望…
The National Football League…
致特别谢意
would like to offer a special thank- you.
向救回马理诺及雪花的人…
to the man who rescued Dan Marino…and our beloved Snowflake.
他是个伟大的人道主义者
A great humanitarian…
一个爱护动物的人
and a lover of all animals:
神探王牌威龙！
Mr. Ace Ventura!
放开我…
Get off me!Get off me!
东 穿上十三号 卖力演出吧
Tone, put that big-ass size 13 on and kick it for the homies.